Guide to the Jeffrey S. Lehman papers, 2003-2005.
Lehman, Jeffrey S. papers,2003-2005
- Series I: Speeches
  - Classes of '30, '35, and '40 Combined Reception, 06/09/05 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Class of '45 Dinner, 06/09/05 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - The Olin Lecture Introduction, 06/10/05 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Class of '75 30th Reunion Reception, 06/10/05 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Class of '55 Dinner, 06/10/05 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Class of 1985 Reception, 06/11/05 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Class of '65 Lunch, 06/11/05 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Class of 1980 Dinner, 06/11/05 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Tompkins County Area Development, 06/13/05 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - President Lehman's Farewell Remarks, 06/28/05 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Jeffrey S. Lehman on Affirmative Action, 10/18/05; 698 (Box 5)
  - Jeffrey S. Lehman on Affirmative Action, 10/18/05; 5545 (Box 5)
  - DVD of three speeches, Inauguration, October 16, 2003; Commencement, May 30, 2004; and the State of the University address, 10-29-2004., 2003, 2004; 82 (Box 5)
- Unsorted material (Box 5)
  - Reflections on the Call to Engagement by Jeffrey S. Lehman, October 2004 (Box 5)
  - Call to Engagement - Questions and Call Responses in Chronological Order, 2003-2005 (Box 6)
  - Letters of congratulation to Lehman at Michigan on accepting the job as President of Cornell (Box 5)
  - Photographs (Box 5)
  - Paperweight (Box 5)
  - Unsorted reports and correspondence (Box 5)
  - COFHE 568 (President's Group) Agreement, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Teagle Foundation, 2005 (Box 5)
  - King/SUNY, 2005 (Box 5)
  - Asia Trip, June and July 2004 (Box 5)
  - Asia Trip, November 2004 (Box 5)
  - CCTEC and Tsinghua University, November 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Proposed Cornell-Chinese Academy of Sciences Collaboration, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Michael Zak/Sherm Cochran Proposed China Center, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Beide Delegation Visit, February 1-3, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)